Guide to the William Rose Benét Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1897-1955; 1922-1950; Series I; 22.43; 50 boxes
  - General Correspondence
    - Schull, Joseph, undated (Box 38, Folder 1523)
    - Schultz, William Eben, 1947; 1949 (Box 38, Folder 1524)
    - Scott, Evelyn, 1929–1948 (Box 38, Folder 1525-1526)
    - Scott, Evelyn, 1949, undated (Box 39, Folder 1527)
    - Scott, Winfield Townley, 1944 April 5 (Box 39, Folder 1528)
    - Scott, Foresman and Company, 1942 September 9 (Box 39, Folder 1529)
    - Scruggs, Anderson M., 1949 June 8 (Box 39, Folder 1530)
    - Scudder, Vida Dutton, 1945 September 23 (Box 39, Folder 1531)
    - Sealock, Violette, 1948–1950 (Box 39, Folder 1532)
    - Seccombe, Mary, 1925–1948 (Box 39, Folder 1533)
    - Seiffert, Marjorie Allen, 1929-1930, undated (Box 39, Folder 1534)
    - Seifriz, William, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 1535)
    - Sekeson, Leon, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 1536)
    - Seldes, Gilbert (to Elinor Wylie), undated (Box 39, Folder 1537)
    - Selva, Salomón de la, 1917, undated (Box 39, Folder 1538)
    - Sergeant, Howard, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 1539)
    - Sessums, A. Cleveland (Alexander Cleveland); Sessums, Elise, 1946-1949, undated (Box 39, Folder 1540)
    - Seward, William, 1948 April (Box 39, Folder 1541)
    - Seymour, Horatio, 1908–1909 (Box 39, Folder 1542)
    - Seymour, Ralph Fletcher, 1934 February 19 (Box 39, Folder 1543)
    - Sforza, Carlo, Conte, 1942 December 7 (Box 39, Folder 1544)
    - Shackford, Martha Hale, 1949 February 3 (Box 39, Folder 1545)
    - Shafer, Chet, 1944 February 28 (Box 39, Folder 1546)
    - Shardelow, Margaret, 1939-1948, undated (Box 39, Folder 1547)
    - Shaver, Chester L. (Chester Linn), 1950 (Box 39, Folder 1548)
    - Shaw, Florence, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 1549)
    - Sheridan, Ida Helen, 1950, undated (Box 39, Folder 1550)
    - Sherman, Leah, 1949 December (Box 39, Folder 1551)
    - Shirer, William L. (William Lawrence), 1945 April 5 (Box 39, Folder 1552)
    - Shirk, Mary Buirgy, 1950 (Box 39, Folder 1553)
    - Shoolman, Regina, [?] September 25 (Box 39, Folder 1554)
    - Short, Christopher, 1945–1948 (Box 39, Folder 1555)
    - Simon and Schuster, Inc., 1934–1947 (Box 39, Folder 1556)
    - Simpson, Maryle Moore, 1949–1950 (Box 39, Folder 1557)
    - Sinclair, Upton, 1944–1950 (Box 39, Folder 1558)
    - Sitwell, Edith (to Elinor Wylie), 1926 June 3 (Box 39, Folder 1559)
    - Sitwell, Osbert, 1926; 1936 (Box 39, Folder 1560)
    - Skeel, Emily E[llsworth?] F[ord?], 1944; 1948 (Box 39, Folder 1561)
    - Skinner, Margaret, 1927-1928, undated (Box 39, Folder 1562)
    - Slocum, Lyla-Yvon, 1949, undated (Box 39, Folder 1563)
    - Sloss, Hattie Hecht, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 1564)
    - Smart Set, 1909 September 1 (Box 39, Folder 1565)
    - Smith, Anne Gordon, 1943–1949 (Box 39, Folder 1566)
    - Smith, Chard Powers, 1932-1949, undated (Box 39, Folder 1567)
    - Smith, Clark Ashton, 1942; 1950 (Box 39, Folder 1568)
    - Smith, Cordwainer, 1950 February 8 (Box 39, Folder 1569)
    - Smith, Lewis Worthington, 1928 October 18 (Box 39, Folder 1570)
    - Smith, P. Bracken, 1949–1950 (Box 39, Folder 1571)
    - Smith College, 1909 June (Box 39, Folder 1572)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1942 July 16 (Box 39, Folder 1573)
    - Snapper, I. [(Isidore)?], 1949 December 8 (Box 39, Folder 1574)
    - Snow, Wilbert, 1929, undated (Box 39, Folder 1575)
    - Solum, Sjanna, 1947-1950, undated (Box 39, Folder 1576)
    - Sorell, Walter, 1947; 1949 (Box 39, Folder 1577)
    - Soule, George, 1946 May (Box 39, Folder 1578)
    - Southeastern State College (Durant, Okla.), 1947 May (Box 39, Folder 1579)
    - Southern Conference for Human Welfare, 1946 March 19 (Box 39, Folder 1580)
    - Southern Frontier, 1944 September 8 (Box 40, Folder 1581)
    - Southwest Press (Dallas, Tex.), 1934 February 19 (Box 40, Folder 1582)
    - Soviet Press Translations, 1949 May (Box 40, Folder 1583)
    - Soviet Russia Today, 1943; 1948 (Box 40, Folder 1584)
    - Sower, Roy Vernon, 1946 (Box 40, Folder 1585)
    - Spaeth, Sigmund, [?] December 27 (Box 40, Folder 1586)
    - Spain, Thomas H., 1947–1948 (Box 40, Folder 1587)
    - Sparhawk-Jones, Elizabeth, 1946, undated (Box 40, Folder 1588)
    - Spatz, H. Donald, 1942–1946 (Box 40, Folder 1589)
    - Speare, Dorothy (to Elinor), undated (Box 40, Folder 1590)
    - Spears, Woodridge, 1949 August 8 (Box 40, Folder 1591)
    - Spencer, Lilian White, 1928–1929 (Box 40, Folder 1592)
    - Spencer, Martha L., 1947–1948 (Box 40, Folder 1593)
    - Spencer, Theodore, 1944-1949, undated (Box 40, Folder 1594)
    - Speracio, Mario, 1948–1950 (Box 40, Folder 1595)
    - Sperry, Willard [Learoyd?], undated (Box 40, Folder 1596)
    - Speyer, Leonora; Speyer, Edgar, 1928-1950, undated (Box 40, Folder 1597-1599)
    - Spicer-Simson, Theodore, 1924-1950, undated (Box 40, Folder 1600)
    - Spingarn, Lawrence P[erry?], 1948–1949 (Box 40, Folder 1601)
    - Spire, André, 1945–1946 (Box 40, Folder 1602)
    - Squire, John Collings, Sir, 1920–1949 (Box 40, Folder 1603)
    - Stallman, R. W. (Robert Wooster), 1946 May 3 (Box 40, Folder 1604)
    - Stanford University, 1938 March 2 (Box 40, Folder 1605)
    - Starbuck, Betty, undated (Box 40, Folder 1606)
    - Starrett, Vincent, 1928–1949 (Box 40, Folder 1607)
    - Stauffer, Donald A. (Donald Alfred), 1947 (Box 40, Folder 1608)
    - Stavely, Margaret, 1946–1949 (Box 40, Folder 1609)
    - Steele, Matthew F[orney?], 1944 June 21 (Box 40, Folder 1610)
    - Sten, María, 1942 June 8 (Box 40, Folder 1611)
    - Stephens College, 1949 August 1 (Box 40, Folder 1612)
    - Sterling, George, 1923–1924 (Box 40, Folder 1613)
    - Sterling, Theodore W., 1947–1950 (Box 40, Folder 1614)
    - Stern, T. Noel (Thomas Noel), 1949 August (Box 40, Folder 1615)
    - Sternberg, Martin L. A., 1950 (Box 40, Folder 1616)
    - Stettheimer, Ettie, undated (Box 40, Folder 1617)
    - Stevens, Virginia, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 1618)
    - Stevens, Wallace, 1933 January (Box 40, Folder 1619)
    - Stevenson, Burton E[gbert?] (to Elinor Wylie), 1924, undated (Box 40, Folder 1620)
    - Stevenson, Candace T., 1949-1950, undated (Box 40, Folder 1621)
    - Stewart, Donald, 1944 March 7 (Box 40, Folder 1622)
    - Stickney, Helen Frith, undated (Box 40, Folder 1623)
    - Stidham, Melissa, 1943; 1947 (Box 40, Folder 1624)
    - Stocking, Fred, 1938 March 19 (Box 40, Folder 1625)
    - Stokes, Elizabeth K. Phelps, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 1626)
    - Stokes, Elizabeth S., 1944-1950, undated (Box 40, Folder 1627)
    - Stork, Charles Wharton, 1949-1950, undated (Box 40, Folder 1628)
    - Storm, Colton, 1938 August 16 (Box 40, Folder 1629)
    - Story Press, 1942–1950 (Box 40, Folder 1630)
    - Strelsky, Nikander; Strelsky, Katharine, 1943; 1948 (Box 40, Folder 1631)
    - Stringer, Arthur, 1947–1950 (Box 40, Folder 1632)
    - Stringham, Edwin J[ohn?], 1942 May 14 (Box 41, Folder 1633)
    - Strode, Hudson, 1929 April 3 (Box 41, Folder 1634)
    - Strong, Austin, 1946-1950, undated (Box 41, Folder 1635)
    - Strunsky, Simeon, 1929 February 6 (Box 41, Folder 1636)
    - Studin, Charles H., undated (Box 41, Folder 1637)
    - Sturgis, Louise Little, 1948, undated (Box 41, Folder 1638)
    - Sturtevant, Ethel, 1929 (Box 41, Folder 1639)
    - Sullivan, A. M. (Aloysius Michael), 1943–1950 (Box 41, Folder 1640-1641)
    - Sullivan, Frank, 1944–1949 (Box 41, Folder 1642)
    - The Sunday Morning Star, 1943 December 13 (Box 41, Folder 1643)
    - Sunset Magazine, 1908–1909 (Box 41, Folder 1644)
    - Survey Associates, 1947 February 20 (Box 41, Folder 1645)
    - Sutin, Helen G[orn?], 1950 February 8 (Box 41, Folder 1646)
    - Swartz, Roberta Teale, 1939–1950 (Box 41, Folder 1647)
    - Swenson, May, 1949–1950 (Box 41, Folder 1648)
    - Swift, Ivan, undated (Box 41, Folder 1649)
    - Swiggitt, Howard, 1927-1948, undated (Box 41, Folder 1650)
    - Swinnerton, Frank, 1927–1930 (Box 41, Folder 1651)
    - Syracuse University Press, 1949 March 21 (Box 41, Folder 1652)
    - "T" general, 1924-1950, undated (Box 41, Folder 1653-1655)
    - Taggard, Genevieve, 1928-1948, undated (Box 41, Folder 1656-1657)
    - Taggart, Jay P. (Jay Paul), 1949 January (Box 41, Folder 1658)
    - Taraldsen, Stella, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 1659)
    - Tate, Allen, 1934–1950 (Box 41, Folder 1660)
    - Taylor, Deems, 1914-1944, undated (Box 41, Folder 1661)
    - Taylor, Francis Henry, 1950 March 7 (Box 41, Folder 1662)
    - Taylor, G. A., 1936-1950, undated (Box 41, Folder 1663)
    - Clipping removed from Taylor, G. A., 1936 April 22 (Box 114 (Oversize), Folder 3333)
    - Taylor, May Henderson, 1943–1949 (Box 41, Folder 1664)
    - Taylor, Prentiss, 1929-1950, undated (Box 41, Folder 1665)
    - Taylor, Rachel Annand, 1928 (Box 41, Folder 1666)
    - The Tea and Coffee Trade Journal, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 1667)
    - Teasdale, Sara, 1923-1933, undated (Box 41, Folder 1668)
    - Tennant, Stephen, 1927-1950, undated (Box 41, Folder 1669)
    - Tewson, W. Orton, 1928 December 17 (Box 42, Folder 1670)
    - Thayer, Mary Dixon, 1928 March (Box 42, Folder 1671)
    - Therese, M[arie?], 1949 (Box 42, Folder 1672)
    - Thierry, James Francis, undated (Box 42, Folder 1673)
    - This Month, 1944; 1946 (Box 42, Folder 1674)
    - This Week Magazine, 1948 Janaury 9 (Box 42, Folder 1675)
    - Thoma, Richard, 1932-1949, undated (Box 42, Folder 1676)
    - Thomajan, Puzant Kevork, undated (Box 42, Folder 1677)
    - Thomas, Cora de la Matyr, 1943, undated (Box 42, Folder 1678)
    - Thomas, Katharine Garford, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 1679)
    - Thomas, Martha Banning, 1914–1950 (Box 42, Folder 1680)
    - Thomas Y. Crowell Company, 1944-1950, undated (Box 42, Folder 1681-1685)
    - Thompson, Dorothy, 1942-1950, undated (Box 42, Folder 1686)
    - Thompson, Dorothy Brown, 1947; 1950 (Box 42, Folder 1687)
    - Thompson, James Alden, 1947 August 14 (Box 42, Folder 1688)
    - Thompson, Randall, 1927 August 8 (Box 42, Folder 1689)
    - Thompson, Walter Roosevelt, 1933-1941, undated (Box 42, Folder 1690)
    - Thurber, James, 1938 October 4 (Box 42, Folder 1691)
    - Thurston, Carl [H. P. (Carl Hammond Philander)?], 1934 October 23 (Box 42, Folder 1692)
    - Tick, Stanley, 1949 (Box 42, Folder 1693)
    - Tietjens, Eunice, 1928–1944 (Box 42, Folder 1694)
    - Tifft, Ellen, undated (Box 42, Folder 1695)
    - The Tiger's Eye, 1948, undated (Box 42, Folder 1696)
    - Tilford, John E., 1949 (Box 42, Folder 1697)
    - Time, 1949 August 19 (Box 42, Folder 1698)
    - The Times-Picayune, 1944 July 19 (Box 42, Folder 1699)
    - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster, 1945–1950 (Box 42, Folder 1700)
    - Todrin, Boris, 1936–1950 (Box 42, Folder 1701)
    - Tomorrow, 1945; 1949 (Box 42, Folder 1702)
    - Tooker, Dorothy, 1949 November 17 (Box 42, Folder 1703)
    - Tooker, L. Frank (Lewis Frank), 1918 October 25 (Box 42, Folder 1704)
    - Torrence, Ridgely, 1935-1950, undated (Box 42, Folder 1705)
    - Town Hall, Inc., 1930–1948 (Box 42, Folder 1706)
    - Trace, Granville, 1945–1948 (Box 42, Folder 1707)
    - Train, Arthur, 1942–1943 (Box 42, Folder 1708)
    - Trausil, Hans (to Elinor Wylie), 1924 June 25 (Box 42, Folder 1709)
    - Tresca, Carlo, Mrs., undated (Box 42, Folder 1710)
    - Trevorrow, William, 1948–1949 (Box 42, Folder 1711)
    - Trombly, Albert E[dmund?], 1949, undated (Box 43, Folder 1712)
    - Trounstine, John J., 1933 January 23 (Box 43, Folder 1713)
    - Trueheart, Rose, 1945-1947, undated (Box 43, Folder 1714)
    - Tuccio, Joseph, 1950 March 30 (Box 43, Folder 1715)
    - Tucker, George Holbert, 1945 January 16 (Box 43, Folder 1716)
    - Tuttle, Stella W., 1949–1950 (Box 43, Folder 1717)
    - Twayne Publishers, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 1718)
    - "U" general, 1929–1950 (Box 43, Folder 1719)
    - Union for Democratic Action, 1944 September 13 (Box 43, Folder 1720)
    - United Service Organizations (U.S.), 1944 (Box 43, Folder 1721)
    - United States. Army. 3rd Service Command, 1942–1943 (Box 43, Folder 1722)
    - United States. Army. Air Corps, 1943 September 13 (Box 43, Folder 1723)
    - United States. Department of State, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 1724)
    - United States. Department of State. Division of Cultural Relations, 1943-1946, undated (Box 43, Folder 1725)
    - United States. Department of the Treasury, 1918–1944 (Box 43, Folder 1726)
    - United States. Immigration and Naturalization Service. New York District office, 1943 July 16 (Box 43, Folder 1727)
    - United States Military Academy, 1941–1949 (Box 43, Folder 1728)
    - United States. Office of War Information, 1943–1944 (Box 43, Folder 1729)
    - United States. President (1945-1953: Truman), 1950 March 7 (Box 43, Folder 1730)
    - University of Chicago. Press, 1947 August 9 (Box 43, Folder 1731)
    - University of Denver, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 1732)
    - University of Kansas City Review, 1945–1950 (Box 43, Folder 1733)
    - University of Minnesota Press, 1948 February (Box 43, Folder 1734)
    - University of New Mexico Press, 1948 November 17 (Box 43, Folder 1735)
    - University of Oklahoma Press, 1943–1944 (Box 43, Folder 1736)
    - University of Southern California. Institute of Character Research, 1935 March 27 (Box 43, Folder 1737)
    - University of Washington Press, 1950 January (Box 43, Folder 1738)
    - Untermeyer, Jean Starr, 1943-1950, undated (Box 43, Folder 1739)
    - Untermeyer, Louis, 1913-1950, undated (Box 43, Folder 1740-1741)
    - "V" general, 1929-1950, undated (Box 43, Folder 1742)
    - Vachel Lindsay Association, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 1743)
    - Vaillant, George C[lapp?], 1944 October 24 (Box 43, Folder 1744)
    - Vallentin, Antonina, 1945-1947, undated (Box 43, Folder 1745)
    - Van de Water, Frederic Franklyn, 1934 December 8 (Box 43, Folder 1746)
    - Van de Woestyne, Royal Stewart, 1942 July 6 (Box 43, Folder 1747)
    - Van Doren, Carl, 1925-1946, undated (Box 43, Folder 1748)
    - Van Doren, Mark; Van Doren, Dorothy, 1941-1950, undated (Box 43, Folder 1749)
    - Van Nosdall, George A., 1946–1947 (Box 43, Folder 1750)
    - Van Vechten, Carl, 1924-1942, undated (Box 43, Folder 1751)
    - Vance, Eleanor Graham, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 1752)
    - Vanguard Press, 1948-1949, undated (Box 43, Folder 1753)
    - Variegation, 1947; 1949 (Box 43, Folder 1754)
    - Vassar College, 1929 February (Box 43, Folder 1755)
    - Veeder, Grace Neahr, 1940-1948, undated (Box 44, Folder 1756-1757)
    - Vest, Eugene Bartlett, 1948 May (Box 44, Folder 1758)
    - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, 1945; 1949 (Box 44, Folder 1759)
    - Victory Book Campaign, 1942 May 11 (Box 44, Folder 1760)
    - Viereck, Peter, 1947-1950, undated (Box 44, Folder 1761)
    - Vijayatunga, J. [(Jinadasa)?], 1949–1950 (Box 44, Folder 1762)
    - Viking Press, 1928-1950, undated (Box 44, Folder 1763)
    - Villa, José García, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 1764)
    - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1945 May 17 (Box 44, Folder 1765)
    - Vinal, Harold, 1947–1949 (Box 44, Folder 1766)
    - Vines, Eda Hadra, 1947–1948 (Box 44, Folder 1767)
    - Vitkauskas, Arejas, 1942 December 8 (Box 44, Folder 1768)
    - Voices, 1945–1946 (Box 44, Folder 1769)
    - "W" general, 1905-1950, undated (Box 44, Folder 1770-1774)
    - Wagner, Charles Abraham, 1930; 1948 (Box 44, Folder 1775)
    - Wagstaff, Blanche Shoemaker, 1944-1950, undated (Box 44, Folder 1776)
    - Wainwright, Jonathan Mayhew, Mrs., 1926-1944, undated (Box 44, Folder 1777)
    - Wainwright, Ruth, undated (Box 44, Folder 1778)
    - Wakefield, Olive Lindsay, 1942–1948 (Box 44, Folder 1779-1781)
    - Walbridge, Earle Francis, 1929–1944 (Box 44, Folder 1782-1783)
    - Walbridge, Earle Francis, 1945-1950, undated (Box 45, Folder 1784-1786)
    - Waldo, Harold, 1929 March (Box 45, Folder 1787)
    - Walker, William J., 1909–1928 (Box 45, Folder 1788)
    - Wallace, Elizabeth, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 1789)
    - Wallace, Margaret Louise, 1949 August (Box 45, Folder 1790)
    - Wallace, Zella, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 1791)
    - Wallis, Jim, 1942–1948 (Box 45, Folder 1792)
    - Walpole, Hugh, 1921 October 13 (Box 45, Folder 1793)
    - Walsh, Chad, 1942-1950, undated (Box 45, Folder 1794)
    - Walsh, Lorna Gill, 1916–1949 (Box 45, Folder 1795)
    - Walt Whitman Foundation, 1949–1950 (Box 45, Folder 1796)
    - Walter, Frank K., 1941 November 18 (Box 45, Folder 1797)
    - Walter, Norma Ross, 1949–1950 (Box 45, Folder 1798)
    - Walter C. Garwick, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 1799)
    - Walton, Eda Lou, 1938 January 14 (Box 45, Folder 1800)
    - Walton, Laura Kinkaid, 1950, undated (Box 45, Folder 1801)
    - Ward, Bertha Evans, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 1802)
    - Ward, Christopher, 1926 March 11 (Box 45, Folder 1803)
    - Ward, May Williams, 1942, undated (Box 45, Folder 1804)
    - Ward, Vernon, 1949 May 12 (Box 45, Folder 1805)
    - Ward, Vernon (Vernon A.), Mrs., 1942–1949 (Box 45, Folder 1806)
    - Ward, William Hayes, 2009 July 10 (Box 45, Folder 1807)
    - Wardell, Bertha (to Elinor Wylie), undated (Box 45, Folder 1808)
    - Warner, Frank, 1945; 1950 (Box 45, Folder 1809)
    - Warren, Fiske; Warren, Gretchen, 1949, undated (Box 45, Folder 1810)
    - Warren, James Edward, 1949–1950 (Box 45, Folder 1811)
    - Warren, Maude Radford, 1929, undated (Box 45, Folder 1812)
    - Watkins, Vernon Phillips, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 1813)
    - Watson, Elmo Scott, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 1814)
    - Watson, Goodwin, 1942 February 10 (Box 45, Folder 1815)
    - Watters, Dorcas, 1946-1947, undated (Box 45, Folder 1816)
    - Waxman, Percy, 1928 December 17 (Box 45, Folder 1817)
    - Weatherhead, Henrietta E., 1949 (Box 45, Folder 1818)
    - Weber, Carl Jefferson, 1943; 1949 (Box 45, Folder 1819)
    - Weiler, Joseph F., 1940-1950, undated (Box 45, Folder 1820)
    - Weir, Dorothy, 1946, undated (Box 45, Folder 1821)
    - Weiss, David G., 1932 October 11 (Box 45, Folder 1822)
    - Welborn, Elizabeth Charles, 1948; 1950 (Box 45, Folder 1823)
    - Welles, Winifred, 1928-1939, undated (Box 45, Folder 1824)
    - Wellman, Rita, 1930-1948, undated (Box 45, Folder 1825)
    - Wells, Carolyn, 1935 September 17 (Box 45, Folder 1826)
    - Wells, Henry W., 1942–1949 (Box 45, Folder 1827)
    - Wengenroth, Stow; Wengenroth, Edith, 1944-1949, undated (Box 45, Folder 1828)
    - Wentworth, Franklin H. (Franklin Harcourt), 1943; 1947 (Box 45, Folder 1829)
    - Werner, William Louser, 1946 October 29 (Box 45, Folder 1830)
    - Wescott, Glenway, 1947-1950, undated (Box 46, Folder 1831)
    - Wesely, Donald, 1947–1950 (Box 46, Folder 1832)
    - West, Rebecca, 1928-1929, undated (Box 46, Folder 1833)
    - Westerfield, Hargis, 1946-1948, undated (Box 46, Folder 1834)
    - Whalen, Will [W. (Will Wilfred)?], 1929 February 13 (Box 46, Folder 1835)
    - Wharton, Edith (to Elinor Wylie), 1925 November 2 (Box 46, Folder 1836)
    - Wheaton College (Norton, Mass.), 1940; 1948 (Box 46, Folder 1837)
    - Wheeler, T. R., 1903-1909, undated (Box 46, Folder 1838-1839)
    - Clippings removed from Wheeler, T. R., undated (Box 114 (Oversize), Folder 3334)
    - Wheeler-Nicholson, Malcolm, 1929 April (Box 46, Folder 1840)
    - Wheelock, John Hall; Wheelock, Phyllis, 1914-1950, undated (Box 46, Folder 1841-1842)
    - Whipple, Jane B., 1947 (Box 46, Folder 1843)
    - White, E. B. (Elwyn Brooks)
    - White, Katharine Sergeant Angell, 1928-1941, undated (Box 46, Folder 1844)
    - White, Katherine A., 1930 August 6 (Box 46, Folder 1845)
    - White, Robert McKinney, 1944; 1948 (Box 46, Folder 1846)
    - Whiting, Lillian, 1935 (Box 46, Folder 1847)
    - Whitmore, Elizabeth, 1928–1929 (Box 46, Folder 1848)
    - Whitney, George Gillett; Whitney, Janet, 1929-1948, undated (Box 46, Folder 1849)
    - Whittaker, Charles E. (Charles Everard), 1949 September 19 (Box 46, Folder 1850)
    - Widdemer, Margaret, 1943-1950, undated (Box 46, Folder 1851)
    - Wiggins, Dolores, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 1852)
    - Wilde, Irene, 1946-1948, undated (Box 46, Folder 1853)
    - Wilder, Thornton, 1928–1948 (Box 46, Folder 1854)
    - Wiley, Paul L., 1945 (Box 46, Folder 1855)
    - Wilkins, E. Michael, 1949–1950 (Box 46, Folder 1856)
    - Wilkinson, Lupton Allemony, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 1857)
    - Wilkinson, Marguerite, 1917 February 12 (Box 46, Folder 1858)
    - Wilkinson, Walter; Wilkinson, Winifred, 1942, undated (Box 46, Folder 1859)
    - William Clowes and Sons, 1928 May 8 (Box 46, Folder 1860)
    - William H. Robinson Ltd., 1927 September 7 (Box 46, Folder 1861)
    - William Morris Agency, 1949 June (Box 46, Folder 1862)
    - William Morrow and Company, 1942-1944, undated (Box 46, Folder 1863)
    - William R. Scott, Inc., 1945–1946 (Box 46, Folder 1864)
    - William Sloane Associates, Inc., 1947–1950 (Box 46, Folder 1865)
    - Williams, B. Y. [(Bertye Young)?], 1947–1950 (Box 46, Folder 1866)
    - Williams, Esther Baldwin, 1947–1950, undated (Box 46, Folder 1867)
    - Williams, Lawrence S., 1935 October 29 (Box 46, Folder 1868)
    - Williams, Marion Rhodes, 1948–1949 (Box 46, Folder 1869)
    - Williams, Nadia, 1950 May 13 (Box 46, Folder 1870)
    - Williams, Oscar, [?] July 17 (Box 46, Folder 1871)
    - Williams, Talcott, 1909 June 9 (Box 46, Folder 1872)
    - Williams, W. L., 1949 (Box 46, Folder 1873)
    - Williams, William Carlos, 1948–1949 (Box 46, Folder 1874)
    - Williamson, Alice Boorman, 1949-1950, undated (Box 46, Folder 1875)
    - Wills, Lois Bailey, 1942; 1948 (Box 46, Folder 1876)
    - Wilmington Poetry Society, 1947–1948 (Box 46, Folder 1877)
    - Wilson, Edmund, 1922-1949, undated (Box 46, Folder 1878)
    - Wilson, Letitia, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 1879)
    - Wilson, Stanley Kidder, 1942–1943 (Box 47, Folder 1880)
    - Wilson Library Bulletin, 1948 February (Box 47, Folder 1881)
    - Wiman, Dwight [Deere?], 1934 December 20 (Box 47, Folder 1882)
    - Windsor, Peter, 1948-1949, undated (Box 47, Folder 1883)
    - Winsten, Archer; Winsten, Harry, 1929 (Box 47, Folder 1884)
    - Winthrop, Stimson, Putnam & Roberts, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 1885)
    - Winwar, Frances, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 1886)
    - Wisdom, William B., 1942–1943 (Box 47, Folder 1887)
    - Wise, Jane D., 1932-1950, undated (Box 47, Folder 1888)
    - Wm. Becker Travel Bureau, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 1889)
    - Wolf, Leonard, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 1890)
    - Wolfe, Humbert, 1927–1930 (Box 47, Folder 1891)
    - Wolfert, Helen, 1950 February 7 (Box 47, Folder 1892)
    - Wolff, Gertrude, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 1893)
    - Wolfson, Martin, 1948; 1950 (Box 47, Folder 1894)
    - Woman's Day, 1944 (Box 47, Folder 1895)
    - Wood, Audrey, 1932–1949 (Box 47, Folder 1896)
    - Wood, Charles Erskine Scott, 1929-1938, undated (Box 47, Folder 1897)
    - Woodhouse, Becky, 1926-1930, undated (Box 47, Folder 1898)
    - Woodward, Robert H[anson?], 1948 December 15 (Box 47, Folder 1899)
    - Woolf, Virginia (to Elinor Wylie), undated (Box 47, Folder 1900)
    - Woolley, Monty, 1940 December (Box 47, Folder 1901)
    - WOR (Radio Station: New York, N.Y.), 1947 (Box 47, Folder 1902)
    - Word Study, 1948 May (Box 47, Folder 1903)
    - World Government News, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 1904)
    - The World Tomorrow, 1927 May 17 (Box 47, Folder 1905)
    - Wright, Betty Ren, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 1906)
    - Wright, Catharine Morris, 1948 (Box 47, Folder 1907)
    - Wright, Conrad, 1944 April 3 (Box 47, Folder 1908)
    - Wright, James, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 1909)
    - Writers' War Board, 1942–1944 (Box 47, Folder 1910)
    - Wrobleski, June, 1947–1950 (Box 47, Folder 1911)
    - Wurtzbaugh, Jewel, 1950 March (Box 47, Folder 1912)
    - Wylie, Horace (to Elinor Wylie), 1927-1928, undated (Box 47, Folder 1913)
    - Wylie, I. A. R. (Ida Alexa Ross), 1929, undated (Box 47, Folder 1914)
    - Wyman, Dorothy, 1945 May 16 (Box 47, Folder 1915)
    - Wyndham, Horace, 1947 April (Box 47, Folder 1916)
    - "Y" general, 1926-1949, undated (Box 47, Folder 1917)